## DAKSH PATHAK

♦ Computer Science Engineer ♦

dp.dakshpathak@gmail.com ♦ 7000472097 ♦ LinkedIn

### **OBJECTIVE**

I am a software developer with robust problem-solving skills and proven experience in creating and designing Flutter applications for a real-time environment. Since my childhood I always had a keen interest in technology and I knew programming is my call. Writing poems is also something I enjoy doing outside of programming.

### **SKILLS**

Languages C, C++, Python, Dart, SQL

Database MySQL, MongoDB Framework Flutter, Flask

Tools Android Studio, Postman, Jupyter Notebook, Figma Libraries Numpy, Pandas, MatplotLib, Sci-Kit Learn, TensorFlow

### **EXPERIENCE**

Software Engineer
Green Rider Technology

Feb 2024 - Present
Indore, MP

Experience in fine-tuning pre-trained LLMs for domain-specific tasks using transfer learning techniques.

Key Skills: Python, TensorFlow, Hugging Face Trans

## Software Development Intern

Jan 2024 - Feb 2024

American Chase

Indore, MP

CGPA: 9.06

Percentage: 77.2%

Percentage: 85%

Experience building RESTful APIs using Flask, including handling GET, POST, PUT, DELETE requests, and managing JSON responses.

Successfully developed an agent task assignment app with real-time location tracking capabilities.

Key Skills: Python, Flask, RESTful APIs, Postman, Git

### **PROJECTS**

## Whizz: Your healthcare companion

A healthcare app qualified for the Smart India Hackathon at college-level, that predicts illnesses based on symptoms, generates reports, recommends doctors and hospitals, and allows you to book appointments effortlessly. Link.

Skills: Flutter, Dart, API, Python, Random Forest Classifier

## Diarify

This notepad was developed in a flutter in order to help you write down your thoughts by playing a song based on the sentiment you express. Utilized machine learning algorithms to train a model using large datasets. Link.

Skills: Flutter, Dart, Flask, Postman, PyTorch, DistilBERT Model, API

## **EDUCATION**

Medi-Caps University, Indore, B.Tech (CSE) (2020-2024)

St. Stephen's School, Ratlam, 12th MPBSE (2020)

Shri Guru Tegh Bahadur Academy, Ratlam, 10th CBSE (2018)

# LEADERSHIP

## Android Developer Mentor, Students Technical Innovation Club (STIC)

Facilitated multiple workshops on Flutter Mobile App development, empowering peers with practical knowledge and hands-on experience in mobile app development.